[♪ sinister music playing]
[screams]
[distorted vocalizing]
[Smee] Wait.
-[screams]
-[Siberian grunts]
[gulls shrieking]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[alien screeching]
[Dame Sylvia sighs]
It's just growing pains, that's all.
[creature growling]
[gunshot]
-[alien screeches]
-[soldiers screaming]
-[soldier] Clear.
-[Rashidi] Are you okay?
It's not safe here, ma'am. Let's, uh…
Let's get you back to the facility.
[Atom Eins] Comms are down.
We think the Cyborg cut
the underwater trunk line.
Yutani is jamming the satellites.
We're cut off.
Nonessential personnel…
have been evacuated.
The hybrids are confined
in holding cell one…
but it wasn't designed
for synthetic beings.
I'm not sure how long it will hold
if they decide to break out.
We have zero containment
on the adult Xenomorph.
Prodigy forces are sweeping the island,
but they're running short of men.
It keeps killing them.
Containment on the other creatures
is good for now.
But we're understaffed.
-And negative variables are increasing.
-[goat bleats]
I think you should consider evacuating.
Sir? Sir?
[Marcy, on recorder]
I'm going to the moon?
[Boy Kavalier laughs on recorder]
No, silly.
You're gonna be the first person
to transition from a human body…
to a synthetic.
[creature bleating]
I wish I could hear your voice.
The things you've seen.
Yeah, that really would
be an interesting fucking conversation.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[clicks tongue]
[grunts]
What did you do?
[Curly] Okay, I know why they're in here.
Don't know what you did,
something dumb probably.
[Smee] Tsk.
But I'm the favorite,
I shouldn't be in here.
-Maybe it's because you snitched.
-Snitched?
-I didn't snitch.
-[Smee] Snitched on who?
They knew right where to find us
'cause you ran and told.
-Did not.
-Wait, did-did you tell on us too?
No, I don't even know what you did.
[Nibs] You're the only one we told.
[Curly] Okay, I didn't.
Maybe if I did,
I wouldn't be in here with you.
[Wendy] We found our graves.
Rose, Marcy, Chris, Aarush…
and Jane.
-You.
-I'm not dead.
She gave us each a flower
and up you go on the table.
[Curly] No, they saved us,
and now we can't die.
Isaac died.
-[Slightly sniffles]
-He died.
[Slightly] His name was Steven.
His mom called him Steve-O.
Okay, well, that's not gonna happen to us.
It could. A fly ate his face!
[Wendy sniffles]
No, okay? I'm the favorite.
I'm not supposed to be here.
No, in the book, Wendy Darling
is Peter Pan's favorite.
And then she grew up.
And that made Peter mad,
and so he kidnapped her daughter, Jane.
We're all in this cell
because we can't be kids anymore.
But they won't let us be adults.
We're all ghosts.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
What do ghosts do?
They haunt houses.
All this time,
we've been afraid of them.
But I think they should be afraid of us.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Wendy screeching]
[alien screeches]
[computer beeping]
[Boy Kavalier] Huh?
Uh…
-[computer beeping]
-No, no.
No. [sighs]
-Kirsh.
-Sir?
The security feeds are down.
Are the creatures tucked in?
We're on our own power supply down here.
All lights green.
I'm acclimating the new Xenomorph.
And the Cyborg?
[Kirsh]
In a holding cell with the brother.
It's risky. Yutani, she'll come for him.
As far as we know, ships are on the way.
Oh, yeah. So you think
I should just give him back?
He came here to kill us all
and steal our toys!
[Kirsh] You're mad.
Don't be mad. Be smart.
Me?
Brain the size of a planet.
Why don't you grow some balls?
She wants to fuck with me?
Yutani, huh? Let's fucking go!
[radio static]
Sir, a defining symptom
of ADHD as severe as yours
is impulse control problems.
And the choices you've made…
[radio static interference]
…the hybrids…
-Kirsh?
-[static]
-[Kirsh] Your medication…
Kirsh? Kirsh?
Morons. They're all…
They're all morons. [scoffs]
How do you feel about your eyes?
Sir?
Uh, find Atom.
Tell him we need to reboot comms
and cameras, and to come find me.
Just to be safe,
I think I'll feed you someone weak.
-[Siberian] Clear.
-I'm fine, really.
Keep the doors locked.
Alert's a hard orange.
We're prepping nonessential personnel
for exfil.
I volunteer to ride the wing.
Knock it off.
We need to find other assets
and secure Mr. Kavalier.
Stay here, ma'am. We'll be back soon.
[breathing shakily]
[inhales deeply, sighs]
It's amazing here.
Everyone is so homely, and it's so cozy.
I'm not really sure. I've got
mixed emotions 'cause I feel like…
I'm not really sure.
I feel like that I'd be able to do really
cool things,
and, like, have super powers.
I'd really like to be invisible
cause then I could sneak up
behind people
and go to really fun places
without anyone.
-[Dame Sylvia panting]
-We'll be okay.
Won't we?
We'll be okay.
[grunts, breathes shakily]
-Hey.
-[gasps]
-[groans]
-It's okay. Let me have a look.
It's the best I'm gonna feel all day.
Let me enjoy it.
[groaning]
[Morrow sighs]
You okay?
I've had better days.
Were you really on that ship
when it crashed?
That's a yesterday conversation.
I don't look back.
You shot me.
I saved your life.
How's the lung?
[intercom beeps]
[Morrow] The boy told me.
Aarush.
Feels good, doesn't it?
Being more than human.
Hermit, there is a price.
When the corporation gives you something,
there's always a price.
Do you know what it is?
-Everything.
-[Morrow laughs]
"Everything" doesn't begin to cover it.
-[radio static]
-Command, this is TR-1, come in.
[indistinct radio chatter]
-Command--
-[shushes]
[clattering]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Siberian] Comms are down.
What should we do?
Protocol is to rally at the armory on one.
With those things running around?
Just fight the battle
that's in front of you.
-Hey. I don't wanna die here.
-Hey. I got you.
Be somebody's dinner?
I didn't sign up for that shit.
Let's just get to the armory
and get the big guns.
[elevator beeps]
Did you call it?
I guess God saved me the trouble.
Come on.
You're letting the cold air out.
-[elevator stalls]
-[bell ringing]
[intercom beeps]
Self-destruct sequence initiated.
-This elevator will explode in 30…
-Open the door! Open the door!
-…twenty-nine, twenty-eight…
-Open the door!
-Come on! Come on!
-…twenty-seven, twenty-six.
Twenty-five, twenty-four.
-Boost me up.
-Twenty-three…
-Hurry!
-Twenty-two…
-Twenty-one.
-Hey. Stop fucking around.
[chuckles] Twenty.
-[alarm blaring]
-[Siberian] What the fuck?
You mad at him?
He shot Nibs.
Yeah, 'cause she killed someone.
-He chose them.
-Yeah, but…
he's one of us.
[Marcy] Dear Joe,
I hope you're good.
Are you good?
We're okay, I guess.
The nurses here are nice,
except one.
She uses the S-word… a lot.
The mashed potatoes are pretty good
and the Jell-O.
Cherry is my favorite.
Dad's been home mostly.
His cough is worse.
And the leg.
He says it's nothing,
but it looks bad, and he can't visit much.
Sorry to say only bad news.
I'm trying to stay happy,
but I get so lonely here,
and I get scared at night.
The radiation treatments are awful,
and I get so sick after.
I wish you could come home.
Can't you just come home?
[Hermit's father]
You gotta take care of her.
Love, Marcy.
[Hermit's father] You gotta take care
of him, don't you, Marcy? Yeah.
[clicks open]
Wait.
Friend, you wouldn't have a cigar,
would you? A nice Cohiba?
Shut up.
Yeah, you're right, but I gotta pee
and this asshole won't unzip me.
[guard grunts]
[grunts]
-[Joe] Oh, shit!
-[grunts]
-Stop. You're gonna kill him.
Don't touch me!
[breathes heavily]
I'm gonna save the ones I can.
You better save the children
'cause I'm gonna burn this place
to the ground.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[cocks gun]
[electricity crackles]
-[gunshot]
-[grunts]
[Morrow grunts]
[grunts]
[both panting]
[breathing heavily, grunting]
[grunting]
-[grunts]
-[breathes heavily]
[Morrow grunts]
[grunts, gurgles]
[creature screeches]
You know the story of John Henry
and his ten-pound hammers?
[grunting]
All night long, he drove that steel,
fighting the machine.
Who can dig deeper, faster?
In the end, man will always win.
It's a question of will.
[distorted] Didn't John Henry
die of exhaustion?
Well, I'm just getting started.
Yutani the younger's troops
are already on their way.
And on her behalf,
I reclaim what is rightfully ours.
[glass shattering]
[creature chittering]
[Morrow grunting]
[Morrow breathes heavily]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Boy Kavalier] Oh, children!
[chirping]
Well, hell.
Look at this sad debacle, huh?
All my Lost Boys…
locked in a cage.
Who am I supposed to play with?
[Smee] You wanna play?
Well, let us out.
Yeah, but will you play nice?
Hmm.
How about a story instead?
[Curly] No.
You're a liar.
You said I was your favorite.
Oh, did I? Doesn't sound like me.
Hmm.
[stutters] Maybe… Maybe I did.
I ju… [sighs] Who can remember? [chuckles]
[Wendy snaps fingers]
What's the story?
[♪ ominous music playing]
Listen. [sighs]
When I was little, my daddy was a drunk.
Hmm.
Yeah, the last in a long line
of mouth breathers,
each meaner than the last.
And to this troglodyte was born a miracle.
A boy genius destined to rule the world.
[chuckles softly]
Unless his jealous daddy killed him first.
So the boy, me, built a machine.
My first Synth. I was six.
I made him, you know, a grown man.
Distinguished.
And, uh…
Yeah, one day, my daddy…
came home from the factory.
And there was my Synth…
sitting on the sofa.
[♪ sinister music playing]
And that was the end of Daddy.
Or should I say old Daddy
because that night we moved
and the Synth became my new daddy.
You see… [scoffs] …no one…
no one's gonna give a six-year-old
his own empire, so…
I just made myself a figurehead.
-You killed your father?
-No. The point isn't who killed who.
The point is I'm running
a multitrillion dollar business,
and that's before people find out
they can be immortal for a low, low price.
[Nibs] We don't belong to you.
Of course…
you do. Sweeties…
you're floor models.
These beautiful bodies can be yours
if you act now, but you're fucking it up.
You're fucking it up!
And I… I can't have that.
-[bodyguard] On the ground.
-[Nibs growling]
Careful now. [chuckles]
Now.
-[growling]
-[gunshot]
[bodyguard screaming]
[chuckles]
Run.
-[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-[chuckles]
[Smee growls]
Hide-and-seek, remember?
Nibs,
you find Sylvia.
I'll take care of Boy K.
Smee, Slightly…
you find Kirsh and the Cyborg.
Curly.
You get the soldiers.
Jane.
My name's Jane.
Nobody touches my brother.
Mr. Hermit. I've been looking for you.
Mr. Kavalier asked me
to find you personally.
He has a proposal he'd like to make.
Your sister is with him.
Please.
This way.
I think you'll like what he has to say.
You think he's still there?
Who?
Arthur.
We just left him.
Don't think about it.
We did a bad thing, Slightly.
It's not our fault.
They made us.
[soldier] Move, move, move!
-[soldiers screaming]
-[gunshots]
[raindrops pitter-patter]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[gasps]
[Kirsh grunting]
[breathes heavily]
[distorted]
Where were you ten minutes ago?
Why is he on the floor?
-His back's broke.
-Hmm.
Take this and tie him up.
Quick, before he comes to.
What are you doing?
Your time is done. It's our time now.
I just want you to know
I didn't hurt your mother.
I don't want to spoil the surprise, but…
I think you'll like Mr. Kavalier's offer--
I'm not leaving without my sister.
And we wouldn't dream of asking.
We're not monsters.
We realize your sister has rights.
Let me guess, the lung's free now…
but you're gonna take everything else.
Go on in.
I'll give you some privacy.
Hello.
Hello?
[creature screeching]
[bleating]
[screech-bleating]
[screeching]
[squelching]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[grunting]
[glass shatters]
Help!
[both breathing heavily]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[Wendy grunts]
I told him it was a waste of technology.
Who would make children immortal?
An eternity of, "Are we there yet?"
But he's a child at heart.
Our founder. God bless him.
Far be it from me to know better.
But were my programming
to allow me to say…
"I told you so."
[♪ dramatic music playing]
-No!
-[♪ music stops]
I say what happens now.
You don't get to hurt us anymore.
Joe. Joe?
What's wrong with him?
He's mechanical, and he's on the network,
just like the doors, and the cameras.
I can make him do what I want.
-Huh. [chuckles]
-[chuckles]
Marcy, I'm… I'm sorry about Nibs.
I…
I didn't have a choice.
You're supposed to help people.
I did.
Nibs was hurting my friends.
-Are you saying Nibs… isn't people?
-That's not what I said.
-Maybe you should call me "it."
-Stop!
I didn't make the world.
You sound like a child.
It's better than being greedy
and lying to everyone.
What would you like me to do?
The world is…
It's complicated. Life is complicated.
You wanna know why I like them?
The aliens.
They're honest.
They're predators.
We're food to them.
No, you're food to them.
I'm…
I don't know what I am.
I'm not a child.
I'm not a grown-up.
I'm not Marcy.
I'm not Wendy.
And I can't be
what everyone wants me to be.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I fucked up.
I didn't know what else to do.
-It's comp--
-Don't say complicated.
That is what powerless people say
to make doing nothing okay.
And I'm not powerless.
We have to go.
We're rounding up the grown-ups.
Where's Boy?
Hide-and-seek.
I've got someone special looking for him.
Whoo!
Okay, this is the founder.
I'm moving to the airship.
My, uh, body man is down.
A million dollars to the first man
that finds me.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[alien chittering]
-[banging]
-[growling]
[growling]
-[Wendy clicking]
-[screeches]
Uh!
-[gunshots]
-[soldiers screaming]
Whoa! I think I pissed myself.
[Boy Kavalier gasps]
A little help, kid.
Huh? [chuckles]
[grunts]
[door chimes]
Stay frosty.
This is a bad place.
I'll take left.
[Rashidi] Security services.
-Anyone here?
-[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[grunts]
[coughing]
[burbling]
[burbling intensifies]
[creature screeches]
-[gunfire]
-[Siberian screaming]
Fuck!
[clatters]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[squelching]
[soldier on radio] Yutani leader inbound.
Prepare for invasion and recovery.
Wendy… darling.
-Whatever I did, I'm sorry.
-No, you're not.
You think you're a good person
who did good things.
All you did is put six children
in the ground.
I figured it out.
Your game.
You're not Peter Pan.
He was a boy who never grew up, but you…
You were never a boy.
You've always been a man.
A mean, angry little man…
who decided to hate everybody.
Just like your daddy.
That's…
[exhales heavily] You gonna let her, uh…
You gonna let her talk to me like that?
Huh?
The plant monster
and the eye thing got away.
But they can't hurt us.
What do we do now?
Now we rule.
[♪ "Animal" playing]
[chuckles]
♪ One, two, three, four
Five against one ♪
♪ Five, five, five against one ♪
♪ Said one, two, three, four
Five against one ♪
♪ Five, five, five, five
♪ Torture from you to me, yeah ♪
♪ Abducted from the street ♪
♪ I'd rather be ♪
♪ I'd rather be with ♪
♪ I'd rather be with an animal ♪
♪ Why would you wanna hurt me? ♪
♪ So frightened of your pain ♪
♪ I'd rather be ♪
♪ I'd rather be with ♪
♪ I'd rather be with an animal ♪
♪ I'd rather be ♪
♪ I'd rather be with ♪
♪ I'd rather be with an animal ♪
♪ Said one, two, three, four
Five against one ♪
♪ Five, five… five, five… ♪
[♪ "Animal" ends]